The Desks list shows all
your service desks Click Create
Desk to set up a
new one from scratch or
from a template
Each desk can have multiple
teams Create teams with their
own timezone and description for
intelligent ticket routing
The Members tab shows all
desk members Add members here
before assigning them to teams
Team routing determines how tickets
are distributed by timezone match
or by AI based description
matching
Working hours define S L
A business hours for each
desk and team Choose 24
by 7 or configure custom
schedules
Desk automation settings control assignment
method status transitions auto-close and
survey triggers
Delete a desk by confirming
the desk name in the
deletion dialog This permanently removes
the desk and all its
tickets