Asset Breakdown by Compliance shows
how many assets meet your
M D M and security
policies Click a segment to
filter the Assets page by
that compliance status
Asset Breakdown by Age groups
assets by purchase date into
buckets Color coding highlights aging
hardware to help with refresh
planning
Software Breakdown by Status shows
your application inventory split into
Approved Discovered and Ignored Click
a segment to filter the
Software page
AI versus Human Resolution compares
tickets resolved by Harmony AI
escalated to a human and
deflected before a ticket was
created helping you measure automation
effectiveness
Agent Runs by Status tracks
outcomes of built-in Harmony AI
agent runs Completed Failed and
Cancelled
Workflow Runs by Status shows
outcomes for your custom workflows
Use it alongside agent metrics
to get a complete picture
of automation health